<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UAV on Yueqian&#39;s Page</title>
    <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/tags/uav/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UAV on Yueqian&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 16:37:33 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ercbunny.github.io/tags/uav/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OmniHEX</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/omnihex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 16:37:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/omnihex/</guid>
      <description> INFO  This page is WIP, as translating the original version of my research proposal is no easier than rewriting one in English. I also need to re-render charts and graphs with Chinese characters, which requires quite a lot of effort. Please expect this page to be complete by Feb 2022. Best regards~
  LINKS   Presentation Of Previous Work (English)
  Research Proposal (Chinese)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Delivery Drone</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/autonomous-delivery-drone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 14:55:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/autonomous-delivery-drone/</guid>
      <description>VIDEO DEMO  PROJECT OVERVIEW   Nothing interesting or related to cutting-edge research. Just an engineering level practice
  Some technical approaches:
 Localization: optical flow, TOF sensor Detection and navigation: YOLO + KCF + Hough Circle Transform on TX2 Flight controller: ACFLY ADRC Communication between FC and TX2: velocity command through serial UART     DETAILED REPORT   View Control and Electronic Circuit Design Scheme PDF (Chinese)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 3-Rotor VTOL UAV</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/a-3-rotor-vtol-uav/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 13:20:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/a-3-rotor-vtol-uav/</guid>
      <description>VIDEO DEMO  SYSTEM OVERVIEW   VTOL is achieved by adding a mixing unit to the F4 flight controller running Betaflight Y3 firmware
  The mixing unit takes in PWM outputs of a basic multicopter flight controller and yields signals for VTOL actuators
  We only implemented attitude control. Communication between boards is via PWM
   Illustration of the UAV | ①: Aileron, ②: Rudder &amp;amp; Elevator, ③ &amp;amp; ④: Tilt Servo, ⑤: Motor</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
