<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UAV on Yueqian&#39;s Page</title>
    <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/tags/uav/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UAV on Yueqian&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ercbunny.github.io/tags/uav/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OmniHex</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/omnihex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/omnihex/</guid>
      <description>LINKS &amp;amp; DOWNLOADS  Presentation of Previous Work (English) Research Proposal (Chinese) Midterm Summary (Chinese) Closing Presentation (Chinese) Thesis to be published on the official platform.   VIDEO DEMO      
 Dev Milestones  Upgrade to ROS2: 100% PID and Newton-Euler Dynamics in SITL: 100% Real hardware drivers and maiden flight: 100% Controller architecture and design: 100% Formulate MPC solver using acados: 100% Test MPC solver in Python: 100% L1-MPC python simulation: 100% ROS L1-MPC node: 100% Track trajectories and collect data: 100% Thesis writing: 100%   Far from perfect, but done for now (May29, 2022)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Delivery Drone</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/autonomous-delivery-drone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 14:55:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/autonomous-delivery-drone/</guid>
      <description>VIDEO DEMO  PROJECT OVERVIEW   Nothing interesting or related to cutting-edge research. Just an engineering level practice
  Some technical approaches:
 Localization: optical flow, TOF sensor Detection and navigation: YOLO + KCF + Hough Circle Transform on TX2 Flight controller: ACFLY ADRC Communication between FC and TX2: velocity command through serial UART     DETAILED REPORT   View Control and Electronic Circuit Design Scheme PDF (Chinese)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 3-Rotor VTOL UAV</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/a-3-rotor-vtol-uav/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 13:20:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/p/a-3-rotor-vtol-uav/</guid>
      <description>VIDEO DEMO  SYSTEM OVERVIEW   VTOL is achieved by adding a mixing unit to the F4 flight controller running Betaflight Y3 firmware
  The mixing unit takes in PWM outputs of a basic multicopter flight controller and yields signals for VTOL actuators
  We only implemented attitude control. Communication between boards is via PWM
   Illustration of the UAV | ①: Aileron, ②: Rudder &amp;amp; Elevator, ③ &amp;amp; ④: Tilt Servo, ⑤: Motor</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
