<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Yueqian&#39;s Page</title>
    <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Yueqian&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 17:21:54 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ercbunny.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Focus</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 17:21:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/focus/</guid>
      <description> My Live Schedule: scroll down to the bottom for recent updates (depend on onedrive service)
NOTHING REALLY Summer vacation! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 16:32:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>CURRICULUM VITAE Formal CV generated by EUROPASS BASIC INFORMATION Contact Mailbox: yueqianliu@outlook.com QQ: 846524026 Wechat: E846524026 Mobile: (+86)18680286879 Overview of Me Location: Shenzhen and Guangzhou Hometown: Changsha Research Interest: Robotics, Control, Perception, AI, Drones Hobbies: Anime, music and a lot more EDUCATION Delft University of Technology MSc. in Aerospace Engineering From Sep 2022 Harbin Institute of Technology, Shenzhen (09/2018 ~ 06/2022) BEng. in Robotics and Autonomous Systems, Cum Laude Admitted to UCB Global Access Program, but cancelled due to COVID GPA: 88/100 TOEFL: 110/120, GRE: 160(V)+168(Q)+4(AW) Guangdong Experimental High School (09/2015 ~ 06/2018) In D14 during the first year In E3 during the rest of the time Ranked about 4000 in Nationwide Unified Examination for Admissions to General Universities and Colleges (广东省赛区) AWARDS 2022 Bachelor Thesis Best Paper Award, Jun 2022 Cum Laude, BEng, Jun 2022 2021 Second Prize, HITSZ Engineering Contest in Drone Delivery, Mar 2021 Third Prize RMB2000, HITSZ Outstanding Student Scholarship, Nov 2021 2020 Second Prize, National ROBOMASTER Championship, Aug 2020 First Prize, Student Innovation Project Assessment, Oct 2020 First Prize, National Undergraduate Electronics Design Contest, Nov 2020 Second Prize RMB4000, HITSZ Outstanding Student Scholarship, Dec 2020 Third Prize, National Mathematical Contest in Modeling, Dec 2020 2019 Third Prize, National English Competition for College Students, May 2019 First Prize, National Undergraduate Engineering Training Integration Ability Competition, Oct 2019 Third Prize RMB2000, HITSZ Outstanding Student Scholarship, Nov 2019 2018 Second Prize, HITSZ Hackathon Event, Dec 2018 Certificates in Chronological Order (PDF)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://ercbunny.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ercbunny.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
